Hello.
こんにちは
It's black today.
今日黒いね
black.
黒い
It's black.
ブラックだね
black.
黒い
black?
ブラック?
black.
黒い
That's amazing.
すごいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's black today.
今日黒いね
Pitch black.
まっ黒
Are the pants black too?
パンツも黒?
Pants pink.
パンツピンク
picture?
え?
That's terrible.
やばいね
Pink is obviously popular.
人気は目立つね、ピンクとか
Are you doing that on purpose?
わざとそうやってんの?
Do you choose your pants properly?
パンツもちゃんと選ぶ?
every day.
毎日
My clothes are black today, so I decided to make my pants pink to make them stand out.
今日は服が黒だから パンツ目立つように ピンクにしようとか
be?
ある?
Not really.
あ んまない
What, isn't there?
え、ないの?
suitable.
適当
Is it appropriate?
適当なの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's amazing, but black suits you.
すごいでも黒似合ってんね
nice.
いいね
It's blackish.
黒っぽいもんね
No, I feel like there are people who look good in black.
いや、なんかその雰囲気がさ 黒が似合いそうな人 あるじゃん、
Things like facial features.
顔立ちとか
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Ah, this person has a face that looks like a mouse color.
あ、この人なんか なんかネズミ色が似合いそうな 顔だなとか
difference.
さ
Oh, maybe this person looks good with a rainbow?
あ、 この人なんかレインボー似合いそうなのかもない?
I don't know.
わかんないかな
You have a face that looks good in black.
黒似合いそうな 顔立ちしてるよね
nice.
いい ね
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
That black.
その黒
It's fluttering.
ひらひらしてるしね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's transparent.
透けてるね
nice.
いいね
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
How long has it been?
どんぐらいぶりだろ
It's been about 3 months.
3ヶ月ぶりぐらいだね
No?
違うか?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
You don't remember.
覚えてないよね
I guess I forgot one day.
俺1日忘れちゃったんだもんね
I forgot.
忘れた
You're crying.
泣いてるね
Too bad, I have to buy a new one.
や ばいな、新しいの買わないとね
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみて
This is so good.
すっげーいいこれ
What do you think about this angle?
どうでしょうか、このアングル
Look.
ほら
Isn't it erotic?
エロくない?
No, it's not gross.
いや、キモくないよ
That's amazing.
すっげーよ
Is this the underwear?
これ下パンツなの?
Those pants?
そのまんまパンツ?
Those pants.
そのまんまパンツ
Seriously?
マジで?
Are those pants?
そのまんまパンツか
That's amazing.
すごいね
Oh no, those pants.
やばい、そのまんまパンツ
This is see-through.
これ透けるんじゃん
It's not see-through.
透けないよ
Is it transparent?
透けてる?
There is one.
1枚ある
If I didn't have this, I would completely throw it away.
これなかったら完全に捨てるよね
Wow, it's see-through.
うわ、透け透けじゃん
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Sandwich it on top.
上に挟んで
Only on top.
上だけ
That's all.
これだけ
Erotic.
エロい
This is dangerous.
これはやばい
If I saw a girl like this walking around, I'd probably die.
こんな子歩いてたら 俺多分デイクしちゃうと思う
I'll attack you.
襲っちゃうわ
Let's walk a little bit.
これちょっと歩こうよ
outside.
外
No?
ダメ?
Then I walked around and it turned out to be a pervert.
それで歩いたらすげー変態
Exotic.
エキトジック
That's crazy, that's super erotic.
やばい、超エロいじゃん、それ
All the men are coming.
男の人、みんなやってくるよ
It's transparent.
透けてる
These are see-through pants.
透け透けパンツだよ、これ
Open it again.
また 開いて
It's pink.
ピンクだね
pink.
ピンク
pink pants.
ピンクパンツ
Look down again.
もう一回、下を覗き込んで
Peek below.
下を覗いて
From where I am in these pants.
このパンツにいるところから
Are you looking in?
覗 いてる?
nice.
いいね
Are you peeking?
覗いてる?
nice.
いいね
Take a look.
覗いてて
I'm peeking in.
覗いてるね
Turn back a little.
ちょっと後ろを向いて
Put your hand there.
手をそこについてよ
Previous.
前の
Push it out.
押し切り出して
That's crazy, I want to put it in the back like this.
やばい、このままバックで入れたいな
You like bags, right?
バック好きでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
What is this black?
何、この黒いの?
この黒いの何?
The black one on it.
ついてる黒いの
The pill is coming off these pants.
このパンツから毛玉取れてる
The pill is coming off.
毛玉取れてる
My pants are pilling.
パ ンツ、毛玉取れてる
what up?
どうした?
pants, pill
パンツ、毛玉
It's taken.
取 れてる
Push it out and cut it out.
押 し 切り出してよ
nice.
いいね
I want to put it in like this.
このまま入れたいな
Okay then, that's it.
じゃあいいよ、そここそろ
Today.
今日はね
This guy.
こいつさ
This one is a little.
こいつはちょっとさ
I want to use it.
使っていきたいんだけど
this.
これ
It feels good, I guess.
気持ちいいよ、多分
I think it feels good.
気持ちいいと思うよ
How hard is it?
硬さどう?
Touch here.
こ っち を触って
Is this hardness bad?
この硬さだめ?
I don't know, it's normal.
わからない、普通
I thought it was hard.
硬いと思った
Isn't this good?
これいいんじゃないの?
Big.
おっきい
It's not big.
おっきくないよ
Mine is big.
俺のがおっきいって
Am I not this big?
俺、こんな大きくないかな?
I think mine is definitely thicker.
俺のがまだは絶対太いと思う
I'm not this big.
俺、こんな大きくねえわ
Mine is thick.
俺のが太い
Mine is definitely thick.
絶対俺のがチンコ太い
But it's not this long.
でも、こんな長くない
This is long.
長いね、これ
Wouldn't it feel better if it was longer?
長い方が気持ちいいんじゃない?
Isn't this a perfect dick?
これ、パーフェクトチンコじゃない?
It's beautiful, this size.
綺麗だよね、この大きさ
nice.
いいね
Let's use it for a while.
ちょっと使っていこう
Later, I popped it into Cuba.
あとで、キューバーにポンって感じで
I'll go there for a while.
ちょっとそっち行くから
Can I have you go there a little longer?
もうちょいそっち行ってもらっていい?
It's close.
近いよ
It's close today.
今日は近いよ
It feels real.
リアルな感じに
Because I'm going to do it in a realistic way.
リアルな感じにやっていくから
Don't you feel the beheading?
仕首が感じないの?
It feels like being executed, right?
仕首感じるよね?
feel.
感じる
How do I take this off?
これどうやって脱ぐの?
This is normal.
これ、普通にこう
Was it like that before?
前もそうだったっけ?
This is what happened before, Chuck.
前はこう、チャック
Ah, that's right, I removed the zipper.
あ、そうだそうだ、チャックは外したの
This doesn't have a chuck.
これ、チャックない
Shall we open it?
オープンしちゃおうか、じゃあ
Let's go par.
パーっていこう
Do you take off your clothes?
パーって脱ぐ?
Don't take off your clothes.
パーって脱いじゃん
Oh, that's one piece.
おー、1枚なんだね
1 piece.
1枚
That's one super.
スーパー1枚だね
How about you go there?
そこへどうかじゃん
It's one piece.
1枚なんだ
Wasn't it cold?
寒くなかった?
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
cold.
寒い
The room is cold.
部 屋が寒い
Isn't it hot?
暑くなんない?
It's cold.
寒いです
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
Well, you can touch it if you feel like it.
じゃあ、気をかけたら触っていいよ
This is actually better.
ほ んとこっちがいいんだよね
Because, this way.
だって、こっち
This way?
こっちかよ
I'm safe now.
無事になった
I haven't taken a bath yet today.
今日まだお風呂入ってないもんね
I haven't taken a bath, I want to take a bath.
入ってない、お風呂入りたい
Right, wait a minute.
だよね、ちょっと待ってみせて
Pussy before entering.
入る前のおまんこ
Good out.
グッド出して
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Look at that pussy in front.
前のおまんこ見よ
Before the bath.
お風呂前の
Tired pussy today.
今日のお疲れまんこ
I don't like it.
嫌だって
Today's tired pussy.
今日のお疲れおまんこ
Isn't it like this?
こうでしょ?
Tired pussy today.
今日のお疲れまんこ
I'm tired.
疲れてる
Today's pussy.
今日のおまんこ
a.
あ
Amazing muscle.
すげえ筋
Why are you wet?
なんで濡れてんの?
here.
ここ
No, no.
違う違う
There are wet marks.
濡れた跡がなってる
why?
なんで?
Did something happen?
何かあったの?
today.
今日
Ray, were you molested?
レイ、痴漢されたの?
Because, look.
だってほら
why?
なんで?
what happened?
どうしたの?
this.
これ
what happened?
どうしたの?
this.
これ
Where did you get wet?
どこで濡れたの?
this.
これ
At home.
家で
Did you get wet at home?
家で濡れたの?
Just watch some TV.
なんか、テレビ見て
That's nice, I guess.
いいなぁ、みたいな
real?
ほ んと?
real.
ほんと
That's strange.
おかしいね
strange.
おかしい
Bring it out more like this.
もっとこうやって出して
It's okay because it won't fall.
落ちないから大丈夫だよ
I want to enter.
入りたい
I'll go in, but wait a moment.
入るけど、ちょっと待って
Oukun, Oma
おうくん、おま
Right?
ん こでしょ?
Oh-kun, it's a pussy, right?
おうくん、おまんこでしょ?
Isn't it a pussy?
お ま ん こ じゃない の?
I'm getting wet.
濡れてきた
濡れてきたよ
About grated.
おろしについて
Something that feels good.
気持ちいいやつ
copper?
どう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
oh?
お?
Huh?
あれ?
Open it properly.
開いてちゃんと
I'm getting wet.
濡れてきた
Huh?
あれ?
oh?
お?
Want to make it a little stronger?
もうちょっと強くする?
terrible.
やばい
I'm getting really wet.
すげえ濡れてきた
My pussy was showing through.
おまんこ透けてきた
terrible.
やばい
It gets wet easily.
濡れやすいね
Let's max it out.
マックスにしちゃおう
Have this.
これ持ってて
My boobs came out.
おっぱい出てきた
Have your breasts gotten bigger?
おっぱい大きくなった?
It hasn't happened.
なってない
big.
大きい
Isn't it possible to lick your own breasts?
自分のおっぱい舐められるんじゃない?
I can't be fooled.
舐められないよ
Try licking it.
舐めてみて
Can't you lick me?
舐められない?
Because it won't reach you.
届かないから
I haven't licked it.
舐めてない
Can't reach it?
届かない?
Can I lick you?
舐めてきていい?
Make it deeper.
もっと深くして
Put it on my finger.
俺の指に当てて
Kuru-chan, here.
クルちゃん、ここ
Put it inside your finger?
指の中入れる?
Can I put it inside your pussy?
おまんこの中入れる?
refer to?
指?
Pussy
おまん
child.
こ
I'm here for a moment.
ちょっと ここ入ってる
My pussy has what I like in it.
おまんこ、好きなの入ってる
Yo.
よ
Iku-chan in pants.
パ ンツのいくっちゃん
Take off your pants
パ ンツ取っちゃお
cormorant.
う
Are you not cantorling?
なんか カントルしてない?
Your pussy pants are so erotic.
おまんこのパンツがエロいね
Show me that.
それ見せて
Show me the back of your pants.
パンツ裏見せて
It's dirty, isn't it?
汚れてるでしょ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけちょっとだけ
Show me how dirty it is.
汚れてるの見せて
It's not dirty.
汚れてないじゃん
Not dirty.
汚れてない
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
It's not dirty.
汚れてないじゃん
It's okay because it's not dirty.
汚れてないから大丈夫
Guess the bonus.
おまけ当ててって
You guys.
おまえら
Was it nice to wear it?
着るよかった?
Why did you stop there?
なんでそっち止まったの?
show me.
見せて
You had a tired pussy today, didn't you?
今日のお疲れまんこだったでしょ、
now.
今
I want to take a bath.
浴びたい
Wait a minute before you take a bath.
ちょっと浴びる前に、待って
Before taking a bath.
浴びる前にさ
Pussy, can I guess that?
おまんこ、それ当てていいの?
Shouldn't it be too long?
長めにならずか
I can see that you can't teach it.
それで教えないのが見える
Ah, this is good.
あ、これいい
This is perfect.
これ完璧
Can you raise your head a little more?
もうちょい頭を上にあげれる?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Ah, this is really good.
あ、これめっちゃいい
Oh, it came, it came.
あ、来た来た来た
this.
これ
Hold it for a while.
ちょっと持ってて
There's nothing I can do.
どうしようもない
I'll do this.
これでやるね
What is that?
なにそれ?
Kusuko.
くすこ
What is that?
なにそれ?
Kusuko-chan.
くすこちゃん
What is that?
なにそれ?
Do you want to see inside my pussy?
おまんこの中見るか
Hey, I don't have any lotion.
ちょっとさ、ローションないからさ、
I'll put it in with my drool.
よだれで入れるね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what?
なに?
What is that?
なにそれ?
Kusuko.
くすこ
picture?
え?
Have you never entered it?
入れたことないの?
do not have.
ない
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言って
I think it probably won't hurt.
多分痛くないと思う
Wow, my pussy is white.
すげえ、まんこ白いの出てきてるよ
You can stop that.
それ止めていいよ
It certainly looks like a clicker.
確かにクリカみたいかも
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛くないでしょ
But I don't think I feel anything.
でもなんも感じないと思う
Don't you feel it?
感じなくない?
feel?
感じる?
Something.
なんか
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
The one you do at the hospital.
病院でやるやつ
Because this is open.
これ開いてるから
It's spreading, isn't it?
広がってるでしょ
Pussy.
まんこ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is it spreading?
広がってる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
What are you doing now?
なにやってんの今?
It's just expanding.
広げてるだけだから
It feels like it's expanding.
広がってるでしょ感覚
Don't you know anything?
なんもわかんないの?
lie?
うそ?
It's kind of like a hospital.
なんか病院みたい
You are coming to the hospital.
病院来てる君が
Okay, about this.
よし、こんぐらいかな
It feels like you're in a hospital, right?
病院にいる感じでしょ?
Yes, it will feel like that.
そう、そんな感じになるから
That's how it feels intuitively.
感覚的にはそんな感じ
It's kind of like what I'm doing at the hospital.
病院でちょっとやってる感じ
What would you like to see?
ちょっと見たいこと?
Are you going to take a picture of that?
それ撮るの?
So I want to see inside.
それで中まで見たいの
Inside my pussy.
まんこの中ね
Can you see it?
見れるの?
I can see it.
見れる
look?
見る?
I want to see it.
見たい
Oh, wait a minute.
え、ちょっと待って
We'll be separated, right?
分かれるんだよね
With people who don't want to see it.
見たくないっていう人と
Well then, let's wait and let me match it once.
じゃあ待って、一回俺が合わせてからにしよう
yeah?
ん?
Well, it's dark though.
まあ暗いんだけど
I was supposed to hit the floor.
フロア当てることになって
Can I rotate this?
これ回転させていい?
Wow, that's amazing.
うわー、すごーい
You can see inside, right?
ま ん この中見えてるでしょ?
copper?
どう?
Is it me?
自分だ?
Inside my pussy.
まんこの中
it hurts.
痛い
Let's show it together, here.
一緒に見せろよ、こっち
Wow, that's pretty amazing.
うわー、なんかすごいね
Can you see it?
見えてる?
Inside my pussy.
まんこの中
You can see it, right?
見えてるでしょ?
I can see it.
見えてる
It's wet inside my pussy.
濡れ濡れだよ、まんこの中
まんこの中、濡れ濡れ
amazing.
すごい
It's so wet.
すげー濡れてる
There are people who like this.
これがね、好きな人がいるんだよ
Can you see anything?
なんか見えるの?
Here's a light that can be fixed a bit.
ここでさ、ちょっと固定できるライト
Please wait.
待って てね
Ah, thank you.
あー、ありがとう
I'll bring it one more time, one more time.
もう一回、もう一回こう持ってくるんだよ
I can see it in my field of vision.
すっげー視界の中見えてるな
See you later, I'll show you what's inside.
またね、この中見せてあげるから
Look at this.
見てみ、これ
Rotate it.
回転させて
Look.
ほら
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
This is the uterus.
これ子宮
Wait, which one is the uterus?
え、どれが子宮?
In the middle, in the middle, see.
まん中、まん中、ほら
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
Oh yeah, that's the uterus.
そうそう、それ子宮
Is this a uterus?
これ子宮?
When stillness reaches here, you will enter a warm funeral and become pregnant.
ここに静止が届くと、暖葬に入って妊娠するから
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
amazing.
すごい
Does it usually stop there?
だいたいそこで止まっちゃうの?
Look at me, here.
見ててよ、こっち
This system is so tough.
この体制すげーきついんだよ
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
You saw it, right?
見えたでしょ?
This is a pussy.
これ、おまん
Man, this is what would happen if there was.
おまん、ここが、あったらどうなるかっていう
Is it up?
あがってる?
My legs don't move much.
足があんま動かないんだね
Ah, things are moving, though.
あ、動いてきてるね、でも
Wow, it's moving.
すごい、動いてる
It's moving.
動いてる
amazing.
すごい
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Man, I'm sleeping here.
おまん、ここに寝てきてる
Pussy, Ajijiri.
おまん、あじじり
My pussy is kicking.
おまん、けじるが
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいとこ?
Amazing, it's twitching.
すごい、ピクって動いてる
Can you move your pussy?
おまん、動かせる?
Great, it's moving.
すごい、動いてるよ
That's terrible.
やばい、それ
Move it.
動かして
It's not moving.
動いてない
I can't.
できない
I don't know.
わかんない
What happened?
どうしたんだろう?
Wow, it's moving.
すごい、動いてる
I felt like I was moving too.
自分も動いた気がした
Do you feel like it moved?
動いた気がする?
I felt like it, but I don't know how I made it work.
気がしたけど、どうやって動かしたかわからない
Wow, that was jaw-dropping.
すごい、あごいた
My jaw is moving.
あごいた、動いてる
It's moving a lot.
めっちゃ動いてる
When you smile, you move a lot.
笑うとめっちゃ動く
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
This is terrible.
これやばいな
Well then, there you have it.
じゃあ、これでね
You remember now, right?
今、覚えたでしょ?
My current pussy.
今の自分のマンコトンなんか
Now, even after finishing,
これで、フィニッシュした後にも、
By looking at it, you can see how the shape of the pussy changes.
見ることによって、 おまん、どう形が変わっていくかっていう
Nohane.
のは ね
I want to take a look.
ちょっと見ていきたい
Should I take it slow?
ゆっくりやっていくか
If it hurts, tell me right away.
痛かったら言ってね、すぐに
Maybe it's okay?
多分大丈夫?
Just a little more.
あとちょっと
OK
Shall we go?
いくよ?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
feel ill?
気持ち悪い?
Get out of here now.
抜けてよ、もう
Wow, a white one came out.
すごい、白いのが出てきました
Pussy juice.
おまんこ汁
Is this serious soup?
これ本気汁でしょ?
I'm seriously juiced.
本気汁ついてる
how was it?
どうだった?
A new feeling.
新しい感覚
Yeah.
うん
No, that's amazing.
いや、すごい
Can I put my dick in a little more?
もうちょっと、ちんちん入れていい?
Leave it like this.
このまま
Once.
一回
Yeah.
うん
Can I enter it once?
一回入れていい?
Will I fit in?
入るかな?